

Profile

A competent network administrator with more than 9 years of work experience within the information technology industry, looking for a challenging position in a reputable company where I can use my skills to their full potential.

Contact

Mobile:

+201270730987

Phone:

+20242211934

WEBSITE:

https://loca-eg.com/Botrous

EMAIL:

botrous.yousseif@loca-eg.com

Botrous Yousseif

System Administrator & web developor

EDUCATION

- November 2024 PHP Full Stack Developer.
- December 2020 Certified Microsoft Exchange Server (MCSE)
- November 2020 Studies Exchange Server
- October 2020 Certified Microsoft Windows Server 2016 (MCSA)
- January 2020 Certificate from CLSLearning Solutions on UNIX7 System Administration
- October 2019 Intensive Training Program on Optical Fiber Network Installation from NT.I
- April 2019 Certificate of Achievement from YAT Center for M.C.S.A Windows Server 2016
- April 2019 Microsoft Certificate of Achievement for Identity with Windows Server 2016 (Course 20-742)
- February 2019 Microsoft Certificate of Achievement for Networking with Windows Server 2016 (Course 20 - 741)
- January 2019 Microsoft Certificate of Achievement for Installation, Storage, and compute with Windows Server 2016 (Course 20-740)
- October 2017 Certificate in N+& CCNA&
 WNDOWS SERVER 2008 from CairoUniversity.

Information Personal

Date of Birth: 12/9/1980 Marital Status: Single Nationality: Egyptian Military Service: Exempted

- 2002 Certificate in Hardware and Software from Centre of FATMAHELZAHRAA
- 2001 Graduated from Egypt Institute for Studies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- From November 2023 to August 2024 in Church of the Virgin Mary in Zenon.
- From September 2023 To November 2023 Laptop Maintenance at AlBatool Company, Queen Mall From 2015 to September 2023 Network Administrator in Crosslinks Company. Key Responsibilities.
 - > Designing and Deploying Exchange Server.
 - Welding methods and conductors (Splicing and Termination).
 - > Designing and connecting internal networks and data centers.
 - Design and connect networks fiber homes (F.T.T.H Installation).
 - > Tests and reporting.
 - > Operate and maintain Microsoft Windows Server (2003, 2008, 2012 and 2016) and Storage Devices.
 - > Active Directory, NewTree, Child Active Directory, AD Partitions, User Delegation, Install AD using answer file, iSCSI, Sharing Permissions, Demote Active Directory, Offline Sharing,
 - Containers and Docker, Shadow Copy, Data Backup, WSUS, WDS, Hyper-V, DHCP, DNS, NAT, VPN, Print Server, GPO, AD CS, ADFS, BitLocker, EFS, Firewall.

- Provide in-person and remote IT support to customers as part of a team or working solo acrossmultiple networks and acrossmultiple facilities and locations.
- > Troubleshoot, diagnose and resolve issues with LAN functionality and connectivity.
- > Troubleshoot, diagnose and resolve issues with Windows Operating Systems, desktops, laptops, printers, and other standard office equipment; depending on location and staffing.
- > Troubleshoot, diagnose and resolve software issues with MS Office and Outlook.
- Install Hardware Devices (Access Controls, Cameras and Network Equipment).
- Configure Cisco network devices (routers and switches)
- From 2011 to 2015 was working as a freelancer.
- From 2008 to 2011 was working in Jordan.
- From 2004 to 2008 was working in a gold factory.
- From 2002 to 2004 was working as a freelancer.
- From 2001 to 2002 was working as. IT technician for Andalusia Company.

Hobbies

- Music
- Reading
- Sports